cyberdust.com 2018-11-04

# Privacy Policy | Dust | A safer place to text

**June 15th, 2016**

We at Radical App, LLC ("Us" or "We") the software developer of the mobile application Dust ("Dust") respect the privacy rights of our users and are committed to protecting the personal information collected about you. To further this commitment, we have adopted this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to guide how we collect, store, and use the information you provide us.

### 1\. INTRODUCTION

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Radical App, LLC through the use of Dust and our subsidiaries (collectively, "Radical App" or "Dust") when you use our websites, mobile applications and other online products and services (collectively, the "Services") or when you otherwise interact with us.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy. You should review this policy whenever you access the Services.

### 2\. SCOPE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Radical App reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy, our Terms of Service, or our Community and User Guidelines, simply by posting such change, update or modification on the our website ("Site"). Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. Your continued use of any of our Site or Service will signify your acceptance of these changes.

If you access our applications from a third party Social Networking Site ("SNS"), you may be required to also read and accept the SNS Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.

### 3\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect information you provide directly to us when you create your account. This may include your username, password, email address, phone number, age and any other information you choose to provide.

With your authorization, we may also have access to your contact list(s) (e.g. so you may find friends) or photo roll(s) (e.g., so you may send photos).

### 4\. HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU 

We may collect information about you in any one or more of the following ways:

#### 4.1. Information Collected Automatically

We may collect usage Information, including time, date, sender and recipient of message, the number of messages sent and received, and the amount of time you spend on Dust. We may collect information about your use of our websites, including your browser type and language, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the website you visited before navigating to our websites.

#### 4.2. Cookies and Automated Information Collection

When you access the Service, We collect certain technical information in order to analyze the usage of our Sites and Services and provide a more personalized experience. We and service providers acting on our behalf, such as Google Analytics, use Log Files and tracking technologies to collect and analyze certain types of technical information, including cookies, IP addresses, device type, device identifiers, browser types, browser language, referring and exit pages, and URLs, platform type, the number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time of activity on our application, and other similar information. In some cases, We will associate this information with your user ID number for our internal use.

#### 4.3. Other Sources

We may collect or receive information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services.

### 5\. USING YOUR INFORMATION

In general, We use your information to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience.

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to maintain and improve our Services, provide customer service; send you notices and updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages, and communicate with you about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards, and events offered by Dust and others, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you. We will also use the information to detect, investigate and/or prevent fraudulent, unauthorized or illegal activity, and carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.

#### 5.1. Use and Disclosure of Information and Content

Your information may be accessed, if accessible, as necessary to provide the Services and may be disclosed: (i) when We have a good faith belief that We are required to disclose the information in response to legal process (for example, a court order, search warrant or subpoena); (ii) to satisfy any applicable laws or regulations, (iii) where We believe that the Service is being used in the commission of a crime, including to report such criminal activity or to exchange information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction; (iv) when We have a good faith belief that there is an emergency that poses a threat to the health and/or safety of you, another person or the public generally; and (v) in order to protect the rights or property of Radical App, including to enforce our Terms of Service.

#### 5.2. Subpoena compliance

If We are served with a subpoena or other official demand by a government agency and We have a good faith basis to believe that We are required to do so, we may grant access to our servers or turnover information, which may include your information and content, but only to the limited extent expressly required under such subpoena or official demand, and only to the extent it may be temporarily resident on our servers in accordance with the procedures and safeguards described below or implemented by us.

#### 5.3. Unauthorized Access

While we take reasonable precautions to prevent unauthorized access to our servers, it is possible that an intruder may access our servers and decode our encryptions; therefore, we cannot be responsible or liable for the removal or deletion of (or the failure to remove or delete) any of your messages. In addition, we temporarily collect, process and store the contents of your messages on the devices of recipients. We cannot guarantee that deletion always occurs within a particular time frame, nor can we prevent others from taking screenshots of your messages. If we detect that the recipient has taken a screenshot, we will attempt to notify you within the application. **You should not use Dust if you require a guarantee that the recipient cannot copy your message, if it exists, by taking a screenshot or otherwise, that our servers or the recipient’s device cannot be accessed by some unauthorized or illegal act or that your information and content, if it exists, will not be disclosed if subpoenaed legally demanded by a court of law or other governmental authority.**

#### 5.4. Sale or Merger

In the event that Radical App undergoes a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, We may transfer all of your information, including personal information, to the successor organization in such transition.

### 6\. COLLECTION AND USE OF CHILDREN'S PERSONAL INFORMATION

Our Sites and Services are not intended for children under the age of 13 and We do not knowingly collect any personal information from such children. Children under the age of 13 should not use our services or Dust at any time. In the event that We learn that We have inadvertently gathered personal information from children under the age of 13, We will take reasonable measures to promptly erase such information from our records.

### 7\. SAFEGUARDS

We strive to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of the personal information. We collect and store information about our account holders as well as the content created by our account holders. Personal information collected by Us is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public and that are only accessible by authorized employees. Usernames, passwords, and phone numbers collected are stored as unique mathematical representations or #hashes.

When you send a message or post content using our Services, it is stored temporarily on our servers without writing to any permanent storage, and we have processes in place to encrypt and automatically delete the contents of the message from our servers after a set period of time. Our encryption model can be found at /encryption-model, and our messaging model can be found at [https://www.usedust.com](https://www.usedust.com/). Our encryption model and messaging model are subject to change from time to time.

### 8\. LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES

You should be aware that the Site and/or Service may from time to time contain links to third-party web sites. Dust is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. If you are concerned about the privacy policy of a certain third party, We recommend that you read the privacy policy of the website to which you link before you submit any personal information.

### 9\. CONTACT US

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding this Privacy Policy or our information collection practices, please contact our Privacy Policy Administrator through one of the following ways

ATTN: Customer Service

2233 Barry Ave.  
Los Angeles CA 90064
